Yuyang Zhou

Beardsall House, Faraday Road, Lenton, Nottingham, NG7 2BS <u>psyyz14@nottingham.ac.uk</u> 07422 579 764

Currently in my second year studying Computer Science with Al at University of Nottingham.

Interested in all aspects of software development and AI with experience of using Java, C, C#, Haskell, Python, HTML, SQL, MIPS.

Education

University of Nottingham Ningbo Campus

September 2016 – June 2018

BSc Hons Computer Science with Al

First year grade 82

- Experience with programming languages with different paradigms like C, Java and Haskell
- Acquired basic knowledge of AI, and experience with AI tools in Matlab
- Learned the basic concepts about computer systems and architecture
- Understood basic concepts of logic units, and made up a virtual computer with Von Neumann architecture by virtual logic units
- Had an overview of the distributed system and Internet protocols
- Experience with database systems and building web pages connecting to database
- Modules have included software engineering and discrete mathematics

Hangzhou Foreign Languages School

September 2010- July 2016

Overall study ability test: 11A, 1B. (A is the highest level)

Chinese college entrance examination: 636

Work Experience

Binjiang Library

June 2015 - July 2015

Book Manager

- Guiding readers to the book they want
- Sorting books by category and size
- Making the library a wonderful place for reading and relaxing

Research Experience

Research Assistant

- Building neural networks node by node in MATLAB
- Taking a further look into differential equations
- Preparing training samples and testing samples for the ANN
- Applying the ANN to solve linear differential equations

Technical Experience

- Learned Java, C, Haskell, MIPS, SQL, HTML as part of first year programming modules
- Proficient user of MATLAB and ANN related tools in MATLAB
- Experience of using C# in Unity game developing
- Experience of using Python in ANN related projects

Extra-curricular Activities

UNNC Book Club

February 2017 – June 2018

Member of Academic department

- Successfully organized two book knowledge competitions with more than 200 competitors
- Successfully organized a cross-club activity to study ancient Chines poems with officers from Ningbo Museum
- Successfully organized a club trip to cultural sites in adjacent city
- Regularly organized weekly activities such as book reviews, book chats

HFLS TV Station

February 2013 – January 2016

Senior editor

- Took charge in all technique issues of HFLS TV Station
- Edited more than 30 episodes of weekly campus news
- Sold more than 100 copies of CD of HFLS TV Station programs

I also have great interest in various aspects of art like performing and music. I participant in drama The Winter's Tale by Shakespeare and directed drama Thunderstorm by Yu Tsao. I also anticipated in micro-movie production for several times. In addition, I hold a license of piano amateur level 9(10 is the highest).